

RIZKI AKBAR

IT QUALITY ASSURANCE SPECIALIST

CONTACT

0821-7592-1678 RIZKI@MITRASOLUSI.GROUP

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN: WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/ RIZKI-AKBAR-BABAR

PROFILE

I am Rizki Akbar. Currently live on Jakarta. Graduated from Sriwijaya University, majoring Information System with 3,31 GPA. Have been working on dozens QA project with different platform as Website, Mobile, and many more. Easy to work as group. Love to learn something new and work with details. As now working on Mitramas Infosys Global as Quality Assurance Specialist.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT QA SPECIALIST PT.MITRAMAS INFOSYS GLOBAL JANUARY 2019 - NOW

AS QA SPECIALIST RUNNING SIT AND UAT, TESTING WITH DIFFERENT PLATFORM INCLUDING: WEB, MOBILE, DESKTOP, AND AS400

FREELANCE QA AT PT.SOYAKAAI

JUNY 2019 - AGUSTUS 2019

AS QA FREELANCE RUNNING MANUAL TESTING ON MOBILE APPS THAT LAUNCHED IN GOOGLE PLAYSTORE, CREATING DAILY REPORT

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION SYSTEM

SRIWIJAYA UNIVERSITY | 2014 - 2018 GPA: 3.31

SKILLS

- Software Quality
 Assurance
- Selenium WebDriver
- Katalon Test
- Integration Test
- Bugs Reporting
- · Mobile Testing
- Web based Testing
- Python Language for Test
- User Acceptence Test

PROJECTS

INTEGRATION TEST AND USER ACCEPTENCE TEST

AT PT. BUKOPIN, HAVE BEEN TESTING DOZENS PROJECTS USING WEB, MOBILE, AND DESKTOP PLATFORM

SHOX APPS

TESTING MOBILE APPS FOR SHOX APPS AND CREATING DAILY REPORT FOR FOUND BUGS